Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative files maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1970-1981; Accession 1981-A-030
  - New Haven Bicentennial Committee (Box 6, Folder 60 - 61)
  - New Haven Colony Historical Society (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - New Haven Development Commission (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - New Haven Police Advisory Committee (Box 6, Folder 64 - 65)
  - Recycling, Yale: newspapers, bottles, aluminum (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Seven Springs Farm Center, Incorporated
    - Associates meeting, 1976 February 11 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Board of Directors meeting
      - 1974 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - 1975 Feb 26 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - 1976 Feb 12 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - 1976 Jun 9 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - 1976 Oct 26 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - miscellaneous additional information (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - South Central Community College: Regional Advisory Council
  - Student/casual employee earnings reports, Yale (Box 8, Folder 74 - 76)
  - Yale Alumni Fund: reference library (Box 8, Folder 77 - 78)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital
    - Board of Directors: minutes (Box 8, Folder 79 - 81)
    - miscellaneous additional information (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Budget and Finance Committee minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - financial statements (Box 9, Folder 84 - 88)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Pension Investments, Committee on (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Role of the Hospital in Addressing Community Health Needs, Committee on (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Yale-owned residences (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Yale Press Governing Board (Box 10, Folder 93 - 95)
- Correspondence, minutes, and memoranda of Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1965-1981; Accession 1983-A-035
  - Correspondence, Minutes, Memoranda, 1965-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
    - Admissions, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Albertus Magnus College: Fiftieth Anniversary Gift Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Blue Cross/Shield of Connecticut, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr
      - Family, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Review Committee: England, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Charter Revision Commission, New Haven, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Chamber of Commerce
      - Board of Directors, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - General, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Economic Development: Task Force, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Staff review, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Congratulatory letters re: secretaryship, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 17 - 19)
    - Davenport College, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20 - 22)
    - Development Commission, New Haven, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23 - 24)
    - Development Commission, New Haven, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 25 - 29)
    - Dogs: barking complaints, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Downtown Council, New Haven
      - Council Search, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Development, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Executive Committee meetings, reports, correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 33 - 35)
      - Oversight Committee, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - East Rock Community Corporation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Economic Development Task Force
      - Airport, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 38 - 44)
      - Airport, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Meetings and memoranda, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - North Haven Mall, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Shubert Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Union Station, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, School of: Policy statement, 1981-1986 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Graduate Club Association Board, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Graduate Club Association: Finances, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - 31 Hillhouse Avenue
      - Bills, miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Cost reports, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Entertainment schedules, Undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Equipment and repairs, 1971-1981 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Inventory (furnishings), 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Prime Market, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Schedules (blank), Undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Stationary requisitions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Telephone message forms, Undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Time worked reports, Undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - 33 Hillhouse Avenue, Undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Historical Society: New Haven Colony, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Liberty Bell award: Recommendation-Committee of the New Haven County Bar Association, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Manpower Conference, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Mellon Center, Undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Multiple Sclerosis
      - Dinner of Champions, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Executive Director Search, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Society Trustees, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - National Association of Business, Industry, and Rehabilitation, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - New Colleges, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Opera Society, New Haven, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Police Department Advisory Committee, New Haven, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Projects '70, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Rockefeller University: obituary on Walter R. Miles, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Seven Springs Center
      - Board of Directors Meeting, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 84 - 85)
      - Budget Briefing Book: FY '80 Budget, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Material on Center, Undated (Box 8, Folder 87 - 88)
    - South African Investments, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - South Central Community College
      - Embezzlement, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Friends of Legal Services, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Regional Advisory Council, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Subscriptions, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Town-Gown Task Force, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - United Way (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - Board of Directors, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - Board of Directors Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Communications Committee, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - General, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Juvenile Delinquency Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 101 - 102)
      - Resignation, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Search Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Urban League of Greater New Haven: Award, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital
      - Board of Directors, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - Budget and Finance Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      - Campaign, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - Campaign, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 110 - 113)
      - Development Committee, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 114)
      - Executive Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 115)
      - General, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 117)
      - Medical Committee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 118)
      - Nominating Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 119)
      - Nurse-Midwife Program, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 120)
      - Role of Hospital in Addressing Community Health Needs, Committee on, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 122)
      - Task-Force, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Mail Logs
    - 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 124 - 131)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 132 - 135)
  - Telephone Message Logs
- Administrative records maintained by Henry Chauncey, Jr., 1972-1980; Accession 1983-A-036
  - Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports
    - A general, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Admissions, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 8)
    - African Studies, Council on, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Afro-American Historical Society, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Albertus Magnus College, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Communications, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Magazine (Chauncey article), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Magazine and Journal, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Records, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Architecture, School of, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Archival and Personnel Records, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 19 - 21)
    - Archives, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Art Gallery, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Art, School of, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Art and Architecture: Telephone, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA), 1979-80 (Box 3, Folder 27 - 29)
    - Astronomy Department, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Athletics
      - Baseball, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Basketball, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Football, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - General correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Golf, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Liquor, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Magazine, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Outdoor Education Center, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Retirees Policy, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Soccer, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Squash, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Swimming, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Tennis, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Ticket office, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Uniform colors, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Automobile: Officers and official guests, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Aviation Service, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - B: general, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 53 - 54)
    - Baccalaureate Address, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Band, Yale, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Banner, Yale, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Benhaven, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Bergin, Thomas G, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Berkeley College, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Bicentennial, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Black Student Alliance at Yale, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Blood Drive, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Bowdin College Search, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Branford College, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Brewster Chair, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - British Art Center, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - British Invasion Reenactment, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Brooks Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 71 - 72)
    - Brustein, Robert, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Buckley Amendment, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Budget Project, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 75 - 76)
    - Building and Grounds: pamphlet meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Bursary Aids, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Business/Industry relations, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - C: general, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Cabranes, Jose, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 82 - 84)
    - Calhoun College, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Campus Police Department: reorganization, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Career Counseling, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Carillon Committee, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Central Connecticut State College, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Charities Drive, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Charts (organizational), undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Chief Marshal, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Child Study Center, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Chubb Fellows, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Coalition on Budget Research and Action (COBRA), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Colgate University, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - College Day at Yale, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Combined Health Appeal (CHA), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Commencement, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Commencement: Alumni Seminars, reunions, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Communications Board, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Communications Department, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Communications Director: office help, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Comparative Literature Department, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Comptroller search, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Computer Center, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Concilium on International and Area Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Connecticut Building Congress, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Connecticut Limousine Service, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Connecticut State of Comptroller, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Constructive Action Meeting, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Cornell University, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Corporation (Box 6)
      Restricted until January 1, 2029
      - Alumni Fellow election, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 115 - 116)
      - Alumni Fellow Nominating Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - Alumni Trustees, election of, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Athletics Subcommittee, undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
      - Fellows, Election of, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 121)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      - New members, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Council, Yale College: Student Corporation Communication, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Council of Masters, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 126 - 127)
    - Cuban Exchange Scholars, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - D: general, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Daily News, Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Davenport College, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Dean's office, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Development (Box 7)
      - Assembly XII, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 134)
      - Campaign for Yale: Easton, Maryland, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 136)
      - Campaign for Yale: renovation, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 137)
      - Campaign for Yale: "Yale Revisited", 1978 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Development and Alumni Affairs: new officer search, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Dining halls, University, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Directory, University, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - D.N.A., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Drama School, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Timothy Dwight College, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Dwight Hall, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - E: general, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Earth Week, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - East Lyme property, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Edwards Street, 360, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Engagement Book, University: memorandum, undated (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Engineering and-Applied Science, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - F: general, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Faculty Club, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Faculty meetings, Yale College, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Fanton, Jonathan F., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Fire Marshal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Fire Safety, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Forestry School, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Freedom of Expression Report, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Freedom of Information requests, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - G: General, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - German Consulate, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    - German Department, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 169)
    - Gift: Class of 1944, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Gifts, Committee on Acknowledgment of, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - Glee Club, Yale, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Good Health Center, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 174)
    - Graduate Club Association, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 175)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, Inc, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Grants and Contracts, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - Graphic Design, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 178)
    - Gray, Hanna H., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Grounds maintenance, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Grove Street Cemetery, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - H: general, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - Halloween, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Health Center, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Hennings, Basil Duke, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Hockey Association Yale, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - Hockey Rink Renovation, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Holden, Reuben A. (Ben), 1972-1979 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - Holden, Reuben A. (Andy), 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Hospice, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - House sitting, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Humphrey, Sylvia: Stenlia Specialties, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - I: general, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Inauguration speech: special printing, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 200)
    - Information office: Transition, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 201)
    - Insurance Manager, Yale, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 202)
    - International Business Machines (IBM), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 203)
    - J: general, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 204)
    - Japanese Sumitomo gift, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - Jonathan Edwards College, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Jury Duty, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - K: general, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - L: general, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 211)
    - Labor Advisory Group, 1979-80 (Box 11, Folder 212)
    - Labor negotiations, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 213)
    - Law School, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 215)
    - Library, Sterling, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 218)
    - Loan forms, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 219)
    - Lord Committee, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 220)
    - Luce papers, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 221)
    - Lux et Veritas, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 223)
    - Mac-Mc: general, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 224)
    - M: general, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - Mathematics Department, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - Medal, Yale, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 228)
    - Medicine, School of, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 229)
    - Miller, John Perry, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 230)
    - Mory's, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - Music School, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 233)
    - Musical groups on tour, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 234)
    - Musical Instrument: Symphony Patron's Party, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - N: general, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 236)
    - National Humanities Institute, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 237)
    - New Haven Preservation Trust, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 238)
    - New Haven, University of, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 239)
    - New Journal, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 240)
    - Newcomers Club, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 241)
    - News Bureau, Yale, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 242)
    - Newspaper Stringers, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 243)
    - Nobel Laureate Lecture Rights Release, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 244)
    - Northland College, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 245)
    - Nursing School, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - O: general, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - Old Campus Renovation, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 248)
    - Oldest living graduate, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Organization and Management, School of, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 250)
    - Osborn collection, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - P: general, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 252)
    - Parents' weekend, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 253)
    - Parking Department, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Peabody Museum, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - Pennsylvania, University of, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Personnel Department: student employment, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Personnel Director search, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 258)
    - Philosophy Department, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - Photography at Yale, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 260)
    - Pierson, George: Yale History, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 261)
    - Polish Week, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 262)
    - Political Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Presidential search, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - Press Board of Governors, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Princeton University, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 266)
    - Printing Service, Yale, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 267)
    - Prizes, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 268)
    - Prom, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 269)
    - Provosts' office, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 270)
    - Psychology Department, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 271)
    - Puerto Rican students, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 272)
    - Puerto Rico, Governor of, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 273)
    - Q: general, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 274)
    - R: general, 197-1979 (Box 14, Folder 275)
    - Religious Studies, Department of, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 277)
    - Reunions, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 278)
    - Reunion program, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 279)
    - R.O.T.C. (Reserve Officer Training Corps), 1978 (Box 14, Folder 281)
    - Russian Chorus, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 282)
    - S: general, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 283)
    - Saybrook College, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 284)
    - Scientific Magazine, Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 285)
    - Sculpture Committee Meeting, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 286 - 287)
    - Secretary's office, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 288)
    - Security Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 289)
    - Security: Student Patrol, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 290)
    - Sigma XI, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 292)
    - Skillman Associates: members, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 293)
    - Soccer League, North American, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 294)
    - Social Studies Conference, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 295)
    - Society of Orpheus and Bacchus (SOBs), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 296)
    - South Africa: Nkondo, G.M., undated (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - South Central Community College, 1973-1979 (Box 15, Folder 298)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 299)
    - Spoon: Yale Prom, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 300)
    - Stationary policy, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - "Stover at Yale", 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 303)
    - Strike, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 304)
    - Subpoenas, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 305)
    - Summer Term, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 306)
    - Summer/Special Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 307)
    - T: general, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 308)
    - Taft, Dean party, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 309)
    - Travel office, Yale, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 312)
    - Treasurer's, Associate, office, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 313)
    - Treasurer's office, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 314)
    - Trinity Parish House, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 315)
    - T.V. Public Broadcasting, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Typewriter service, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 318)
    - U: general, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 319)
    - Union, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - University Council Community Relations Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - V: general, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Vice President's office, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    - Vice President search, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - Vietnam Memorial, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 326)
    - W: general, 1977-1979 (Box 16, Folder 327)
    - Waste Power Plant, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 328)
    - Watch, gold, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 329)
    - Weaver, Howard S., 1973-83 (Box 16, Folder 330)
    - Weekly Bulletin and Calendar, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - Whiffenpoofs, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - Women's Caucus, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - Women, Office on the Education of, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - Women's Forum Week, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - Women's Information and Counseling Service, undated (Box 17, Folder 337)
    - Woodbridge Hall paintings, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 338)
    - WYBC, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 339)
    - X-Y-Z: general, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 340)
    - Yale animal, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 341)
    - Yale Coat of Arms, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 342)
    - Yale Co-operative Corporation, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 343)
    - Yale Dames, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 344)
    - Yale Psychiatric Institute (YPI), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 345)
    - Yale Scene Series, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 346)
    - Yale Seal, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 347)
    - Yale Symphony Orchestra, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 348)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 18)
      - Board of Directors, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 349)
      - Executive Search, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 350)
      - General, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 351)
      - Nominating Committee, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 352)
      - Revitalization Conference, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 353)
    - Connecticut Savings Bank, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 354)
    - Historical Society, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 355)
    - South Central Community College (Box 18)